Railway Labor Executives' Association Additional Records 5728
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series VI: Office Files, 1977
  - Other Organizations: American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (General), 1977 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    Includes Proceeding of the 12th Annual AFL-CIO Constitutional Convention, a report written by the RLEA to be presented at the convention, and correspondence in re the status of Conrail employees represented by member organizations of RLEA.
  - Other Organizations: AFL-CIO, Civil Rights Department, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Other Organizations: AFL-CIO, Committee on Political Education (COPE), 1977 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Other Organizations: American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) Minutes, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Other Organizations: American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Legislative Newsletter, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Other Organizations: AFL-CIO, Legislative Council, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Other Organizations: AFL-CIO, Executive Council, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Other Organizations: Miscellaneous and General, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Other Organizations: National Safety Council, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 23)
    Includes various pamphlets on home and workplace safety.
  - Other Organizations: Research Institute of America - Recommendations, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - Other Organizations: Transportation Research Forum, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - Other Organizations: The Labor Management Committee for Fair Foreign Competition, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - Other Organizations: Charities (General), 1977 (Box 33, Folder 27)
  - Other Organizations: LABOR Newspaper, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 28)
    Include financial reports and audit report.
  - Other Organizations: Special Election Year Editions of LABOR Newspaper, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 29)
  - Other Organizations: City of Hope, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 30)
  - Other Organizations: National Association of Railroad Passengers (NARP), 1977 (Box 33, Folder 31)
  - Other Organizations: Labor Bureau of the Middle West, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 32)
  - International Affairs: General, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 33)
    Includes ITF newsletters and correspondence. Correspondence includes letters in re Pinochet's military junta in Chile and its suppression of unionists. There are also new reports on the arrest of the leader of the Socialist Party of India.
  - International Affairs: Bureau of International Labor Affairs (Foreign Visitors), 1977 (Box 33, Folder 34)
  - International Affairs: Office of International Labor Affairs (OILA) - Team Managers, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 35)
  - Commuter Problems: General, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 36)
  - Commuter Problems: Philadelphia Service Improvement Corporation, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 37)
  - Commuter Problems: New Haven Problems, including New York Area, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 38)
  - Commuter Problems: Bay Area Rapid Transit (BART), 1977 (Box 33, Folder 39)
  - Commuter Problems: Port Authority Trans-Hudson (PATH), 1977 (Box 33, Folder 40)
  - Commuter Problems: Adequacies (General), 1977 (Box 33, Folder 41)
  - Commuter Problems: Commuter Service Improvements - Housing and Urban Development (HUD) Mass Transit Grants, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 42)
  - Commuter Problems: Urban Mass Transportation Administration - Conrail Emergency Operating Assistance (Various), 1977 (Box 33, Folder 43)
  - Commuter Problems: Section 13(c) Agreement, Massachusetts Bay Transportation Authority, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 44)
  - Commuter: Chicago, Loop and West Suburban - Section 13(c) Agreement, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 45)
  - Commuter Problems: Washington Metro Area Transit Authority, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 46)
  - Commuter: Illinois Regional Transportation Authority (Section 13 Agreement), 1977 (Box 33, Folder 47)
    Employee Protective Agreement
- Series VII: Office Files, 1978
  - Government: Executive Branch, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 48)
  - Government: House and Senate, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 49)
  - Government: Agencies (General), 1978 (Box 33, Folder 50)
  - Government: United States Environmental Protection Agency, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 51)
    Includes newsletters and a report on noise pollution.
  - Government: Department of Transportation [folder 1 of 2], 1978 (Box 33, Folder 52a)
    Includes bulletins and the preliminary report "A Reexamination of the Amtrak Route Structure."
  - Government: Department of Transportation [folder 2 of 2], 1978 (Box 33, Folder 52b)
  - Government: Department of Transportation - Staff Appointments, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 53)
  - Government: Transportation Association of America, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 54)
    Harriman Safety Awards
  - Government: National Transportation Safety Board, File 1, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 55)
    Includes NTSB Accident Reports, press releases, and remarks of NTSB Chairman Kay Bailey.
  - Government: National Transportation Safety Board, File 2, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 56)
  - Government: Federal Railroad Administration, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 57)
    Includes "Final Report on Restructuring the Task Force on Rail Transportation" by Donald Beattie
  - Government: Federal Railroad Administration-Department of Transportation - Project REAP (Alcohol Research), 1978 (Box 33, Folder 58)
    Includes initial reports from Project REAP, the study of railroad employee assistance programs and alcoholism in railroad employees.
  - Government: Federal Railroad Administration - Training Program, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 59)
    Includes Memorandum of Understanding between FRA and the U.S. Office of Education in re starting a continuing education/training program for railroad employees.
  - Government: Federal Railroad Administration Staff Appointments, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 60)
  - Government: Office of Railroad Safety, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 61)
    Pamphlet "Railroad Employee Fatalities Investigated by the Federal Railroad Administration in 1976."
  - Government: Safety - Rules, Regulations, Petitions (Federal Railroad Administration-Department of Transportation), 1978 (Box 33, Folder 62)
  - Government: Safety Appliance Acts, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 63)
  - Government: Highway Grade Crossing Matters, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Government: Power Brakes, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Government: Locomotive Inspection, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Government: Signal Rules, Standards, and Instructions (RS and I Cases), 1978 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Government: Approval of Changes in Signal Installations (BS-AP Cases), 1978 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Government: Hours of Service, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Government: Track Maintenance and Inspection Standards, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Government: Accident Reports and Governing Regulations, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Government: Federal Railroad Administration-Department of Transportation - Accident/Incident Reports, Classification, and Investigation, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    Includes annual reports on railroad accidents for 1976 and 1977.
  - Government: Labor Department (General), 1978 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Government: Bureau of Labor Statistics, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    Includes wage chronologies for union positions in transportation industry and bulletins in re the consumer price index. Also includes Area Wage Surveys for metropolitan areas in Illinois, New York, and New Jersey.
  - Government: Occupational Safety and Health Administration (OSHA), 1978 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Government: Urban Mass Transportation Administration Section 13(c) (General), 1978 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Government: Interstate Commerce Commission - Rail Services Planning Office (General), 1978 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    Includes bulletins, reports on railroad employment, and correspondence.
  - Government: Interstate Commerce Commission - Membership and Staff Appointments, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Government: Interstate Commerce Commission - Rules of Practice and Administrative Procedure, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Government: Interstate Commerce Commission - Statistics, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Government: Interstate Commerce Commission Ex Parte 278 - Equal Opportunity in Surface Transportation, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Government: Interstate Commerce Commission Bureau of Transport Economics and Statistics (General), 1978 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Government: Interstate Commerce Commission Ex Parte 282 (Sub 2) - Railroad Consolidation Procedures, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Government: Interstate Commerce Commission Ex Parte 274 Sub 1 - Special Procedures for Proposed Railroad Abandonments, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Government: Interstate Commerce Commission Ex Parte 274 Sub 2 - Proposed Rulemaking, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Government: Interstate Commerce Commission Ex Parte 293 Sub 4 - Northeastern Railroad Investigation, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - Government: Interstate Commerce Commission Ex Parte 270 Sub 2 - Investigation of Railroad Freight Service, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 24)
    Petition for Review of Report and Order of the ICC, filed by the AT&SF Railway Co.
  - Government: National Mediation Board (General), 1978 (Box 34, Folder 25)
    Correspondence in re funding for NMB and NRAB neutral members.
  - Government: National Mediation Board - Emergency Board Reports, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - Government: National Mediation Board - Public Law Board - Decisions on Procedural Questions, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 27)
    Includes Public Law Board 1998 Award No. 1.
  - Government: National Mediation Board - Membership and Staff Appointments, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 28)
  - Government: National Mediation Board - Rules of Procedure and Administration, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 29)
  - Government: National Mediation Board - Appropriations, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 30)
  - Government: Special Board of Adjustment Number 605, Regarding February 7, 1965 Agreement - Awards, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 31)
  - Government: Arbitration Board Number 298, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 32)
  - Government: National Railroad Adjustment Board (General), 1978 (Box 34, Folder 33)
    Includes list of newly elected NRAB chairs and vice-chairs.
  - Government: NRAB First Division, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 34)
  - Government: NRAB Second Division, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 35)
  - Government: NRAB Third Division, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 36)
  - Government: NRAB Fourth Division, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 37)
  - Government: Organizations Qualified to Participate in Selection of Members, National Railroad Adjustment Board, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 38)
  - Government: National Railroad Adjustment Board - Membership, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 39)
  - Government: Application of Arbitration Awards, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 40)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board (General), 1978 (Box 34, Folder 41)
  - Government: The Railroad Retirement Board - Quarterly Review, October 20, 1978. (Box 34, Folder 42)
  - Government: The Railroad Retirement Board - Quarterly Review, July 21, 1978. (Box 34, Folder 43)
  - Government: The Railroad Retirement Board - Quarterly Review, May 25, 1978. (Box 34, Folder 44)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board - Tax Tables, Calendar Year 1978. (Box 34, Folder 45)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board - Tax Tables, Calendar Year 1979. (Box 34, Folder 46)
  - Government: Reports for Railway Labor Executives Association Meeting from Railroad Retirement Board, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    Includes pamphlet on 1977 amendments to Social Security, a pamphlet analyzing those amendments, and financial reports.
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board - Membership and Staff Appointments, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board - Administrative Practices and Procedures, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board - Field Offices - Schedule of Regular Itinerant Service, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board - Mechanization and Centralization of Claims Payment, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board - Coverage of Railroads and Unions as Employers, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board - Status of Funds, Actuarial Reports, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board - 1977 Annual Report, Statistical Supplement, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    Statistical Supplement. Published June 1978.
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board Quarterly Review, March 9, 1978. (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board Quarterly Review, May 25, 1978. (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board - Service and Taxable Compensation of Railroad Employees, Statistical Tables, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    February 1978.
  - Government: Report of Reimbursements Made by the United States Railroad Retirement Board under the Regional Rail Reorganization Act of 1973, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    November 17, 1978.
  - Government: Railroad Retirement, Benefits, and Railroad Unemployment Insurance Systems, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    Includes monthly benefit statistics, bulletins, and circulars.
  - Government: Railroad Annuities Affected by PL-588 (Veterans Pensions), 1978 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board - Educational Program, Meetings, Films, Etcetera (Scheduled Informational Conferences), 1978 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board - Press Releases, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Government: Supplemental Retirement Plans (Supplemental Pensions), Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board - National Reporting Officers Memoranda, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Government: Administration of Medicare - Financial Intermediary, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Government: President's Committee on the Physically Handicapped, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Government: National Railroad Passenger Corporation (AMTRAK), 1978 (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - Government: United States Railway Association, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 22)
    Includes newsletters in re the Northeast Rail Problem.
  - Government: RLEA Labor-Conrail Subcommittee (Chairman James E. Burke), File 1 [folder 1 of 3], 1978 (Box 35, Folder 23a)
    Correspondence in re the establishment of Special Board of Adjustment No. 880 and Title V of the Regional Rail Reorganization Act of 1973. Also includes brief filed before SBA No. 880 by unions and by carrier.
  - Government: RLEA Labor-Conrail Subcommittee (Chairman James E. Burke), File 1 [folder 2 of 3], 1978 (Box 35, Folder 23b)
  - Government: RLEA Labor-Conrail Subcommittee (Chairman James E. Burke), File 1 [folder 3 of 3], 1978 (Box 35, Folder 23c)
  - Government: RLEA Labor-Conrail Subcommittee (Chairman James E. Burke), File 2, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - Government: Consolidated Rail Corporation (CONRAIL), 1978 (Box 35, Folder 25)
    Includes Annual Report 1977, correspondence in re Project REAP, and newspaper clippings.
  - Government: National Transportation Policy Study Commission, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - Government: Department of Energy (General), 1978 (Box 35, Folder 27)
  - Judicial: Court Cases (General), 1978 (Box 35, Folder 28)
  - Judicial: Penn Central Bankruptcy (Reorganization), 1978 (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Judicial: Boston and Maine Reorganization, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 30)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: General [folder 1 of 2], 1978 (Box 35, Folder 31a)
    Includes copy of Joint Trust Agreement between the Long Island Railroad and railway labor unions. Also includes promotional pamphlets for Project REAP.
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: General [folder 2 of 2], 1978 (Box 35, Folder 31b)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Membership, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 32)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Constitution and By-Laws, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 33)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Travelers Insurance Company, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 34)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Officers and Members, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 35)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: American Railway Supervisors' Association, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 36)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: American Train Dispatchers' Association, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 37)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 38)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Brotherhood of Railway Carmen of the United States and Canada, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 39)
    Copy of letter stating that BSCP will be merging into BRAC on April1, 1978.
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Brotherhood of Sleeping Car Porters, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 40)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 41)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: International Brotherhood of Boilermakers and Blacksmiths, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 42)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 43)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: International Brotherhood of Firemen and Oilers, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 44)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: International Organization of Masters, Mates, and Pilots of America, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 45)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: National Marine Engineers Beneficial Association, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 46)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Railroad Yardmasters of America, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 47)
    Includes copy of "The Railroad Yardmaster" magazine, vol. 60, no. 4.
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Railway Employees' Department, American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO), 1978 (Box 35, Folder 48)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Sheet Metal Workers International Association, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 49)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 50)
    Includes pamphlet, :Vandalism: The Impact on railroad Locomotive Engineers and Other Railroad Operating Employees in the Los Angeles Area."
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 51)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 52)
    Includes correspondence in re the merger of BRAC and BSCP on April 1, 1978.
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 53)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Seafarers International Union, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 54)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Transport Workers Union, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 55)
    Includes reports on planning the 1980 ITF World Congress, and statements on Conrail by TWU Railroad Division Vice-President Albert Terriego.
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: United Transportation Union, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 56)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Meetings (General), 1978 (Box 35, Folder 57)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Miami Meeting, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Agendas, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Legal Cases (Agenda Item 2.1), 1978 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Assessments, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Applications for Affiliation, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Wages and Rules (General), 1978 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Radio Telephone Equipment Communications, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Florida East Coast Railway, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Health and Welfare, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Travelers Dental Plan Group Policy GA-874710, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Union Shop (General), 1978 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Union Dues (General), 1978 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Washington Job Protection Agreement Cases, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Committees (General), 1978 (Box 36, Folder 14)
    Includes list of standing RLEA committees.
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Committee on Legislation and Safety Meeting (As of April 18, 1978 RLEA Meeting) (Box 36, Folder 15)
    In re proposed Amtrak System Safety Program.
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Executive Committee, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 16)
    Minutes of meeting.
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Committee to Meet with Association of American Railroads - Railroad Labor-Management Relations, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Labor Management Task Force on Terminals, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 18)
    Includes pamphlets on intermodal facilities railroads effectively competing with trucking companies.
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Railroad Labor/Management Relations, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 19)
    Folder marked "New File July 14, 1977." Refers to withdrawal from committee by RLEA and labor representatives. The above file (f. 18) contains said records.
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Immigration Problems, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 20)
    Correspondence in re Canadian railroaders working for Conrail and the effects on seniority districts.
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Committee on Railroad Retirement, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Committee on Railway Labor Act, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Committee on National Transportation Policy, Mergers, and Consolidation and Passenger Service, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Legislative Representatives, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Committee on Council of Allied Labor (COAL), Burlington Northern, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Passes, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Prospective Employees (General), 1978 (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Financial (General), 1978 (Box 36, Folder 28)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Financial Statements, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 29)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Lawyers (General), 1978 (Box 36, Folder 30)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Lawyer Bills [folder 1 of 2], 1978 (Box 36, Folder 31a)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Lawyer Bills [folder 2 of 2], 1978 (Box 36, Folder 31b)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Strikes (General), 1978 (Box 36, Folder 32)
  - Railroads: General, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 33)
  - Railroads: Ownership, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 34)
  - Railroads: Auto-Train Corporation, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 35)
  - Railroads: Association of American Railroads (AAR) [folder 1 of 2], 1978 (Box 36, Folder 36a)
  - Railroads: Association of American Railroads (AAR) [folder 2 of 2], 1978 (Box 36, Folder 36b)
  - Railroads: National Railway Labor Conference, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 37)
  - Railroads: Hospital Associations (General), 1978 (Box 36, Folder 38)
  - Other Organizations: American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO), 1978 (Box 36, Folder 39)
    Includes newsletters of AFL-CIO committees.
  - Other Organizations: Committee on Political Education (COPE), 1978 (Box 36, Folder 40)
  - Other Organizations: Legislative Council, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 41)
  - Other Organizations: Executive Councils, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 42)
  - Other Organizations: Miscellaneous and General, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 43)
  - Other Organizations: National Safety Council, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 44)